(Leonard:)What the hell are you doing?
I'm making petri dishes
to grow throat cultures.
(Leonard:)With lime Jell-O?
(Sheldon:)I need a growth medium, and someone
polished off the apricot yogurt.
(Sheldon:)Here. Swab my throat.
- I don't think so.
- Leonard.
If I'm going to get ahead of this, I need
to find out what's growing in my throat.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, you are not sick.
(Leonard:)This is, but you are not.
(Sheldon:)We have no idea what pathogen...
(Sheldon:)...Typhoid Penny
has introduced into our environment.
(Sheldon:)And having never been to Nebraska, I'm
certain I have no corn-husking antibodies.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, don't you think
you're overreacting?
(Sheldon:)When I'm lying comatose in a hospital
relying on inferior minds to cure me...